vonmaur.com 2006-12-31

# Privacy Policy

The following statement discloses Von Maur’s consumer privacy practices for the Von Maur Web site. We do update our policy from time to time without notice, so please check back periodically. All updates will be published on this page. 

Von Maur understands your desire to protect personal information. We intend to inform you how your personal information will be gathered, tracked or used, and give you choices. If choices are not offered on Web pages where your personal information is obtained, please select one of the communication channels at the bottom of this statement to indicate your communications preference. 

We request personal information when you correspond with us. You make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information you may not be able to complete the transaction. 

We use personally identifiable information in the following ways: 

> To provide you with information about new products, upcoming events, or informative e-mails; 
> 
> To assist us in creating content that is relevant to you; 
> 
> To provide you with special offers that may be of interest to you. 

Please be advised that in certain instances, it may be necessary for Von Maur to disclose your personal information to government officials or otherwise as required by our legal obligations. 

Von Maur provides a number of ways for you to ‘opt-out’ of receiving additional information from us. We may offer you these choices at the time you give us your information. If you do not wish to continue receiving e-mail or bulletins you can opt-out of receiving these communications by replying with "unsubscribe" in the subject line in the e-mail. 

We have taken security measures, consistent with international information practices, to protect your personal information. These measures include technical and procedural steps to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, alteration, or destruction. 

We make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to update or correct your personal information. If you believe that Von Maur does not have your current personal information, you can update it by using one of the other communication channels at the bottom of this statement. 

Von Maur may use cookies from time to time. A cookie is a unique text file that a Web site can send to your browser software. Cookies enable a Web site to tailor information presented to you based on your browsing preferences. Von Maur may use cookies to personalize your pages at our Service and Support Web site, or to remember you when you register for products or services. If you do not want Von Maur to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a Web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use of some of the products and/or services at our Web site. 

Von Maur may also use cookies to track your visit to our Web site. While our Web servers may automatically log your IP address, this information does not identify you and you remain anonymous. 

We may track domain names, IP addresses, and browser types from people who visit our site. We use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout Von Maur's Web site. Such information is not correlated with any personal information 

At the Von Maur Web site, there may be links to companies with whom we have a relationship. Von Maur is not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners. We encourage you to read their privacy statements, as they may differ from ours. 

In the event there is a major change to Von Maur's privacy practices, a prominent notice will be posted on our Web site. 

If you have any questions, comments, or would like to change your communication preferences, please contact us using one of the options below: 

Customer Preferences:  E-mail: | advertisingpr@vonmaur.com  
---|---  
Fax: | (563) 388-2242  
Telephone: | (563) 388-2200  
Postal Mail: | Von Maur  
Attention: Advertising - Web Site Privacy Policy  
6565 Brady Street  
Davenport, Iowa 52806
